MONISHA NAGPAL

Phone: +91 9116907334 Email: <u>mn5864@srmist.edu.in</u>

Address: 78 Patel Nagar, Jhotwara, Jaipur City 302012(IN)

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Acquired 90% in CBSE in the 12th Standard, 89% in CBSE in the 10th Standard. Skilled and have interest in Graphic Designing, UI/UX Designing, Web Designing and Development. Have 2+ months of experience in Creative Field and 11+ months of experience in Event Management.

.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Nov. 2020 – Dec.2021 Event Associate Manager, SRM HackerEarth
Chennai, Tamil Nadu Plans details and aspects of the event, including team management, sponsorship and efficient event management.

Aug. 2021 - Nov.2021 Graphic Designer, GeekForGeeks SRMIST
Chennai, Tamil Nadu Design Post, Stories, IGTV covers for Social Media Handle.

Aug. 2021 – Dec.2021 Graphic Designer, The Listening Space
Chennai, Tamil Nadu Create Designs for different screen types and media platform.

Nov.2021-Present Technical Member, The Six PM Show Chennai, Tamil Nadu Maintains the official website of TSPS

Nov.2021-Present Technical Member, NWC Association Chennai, Tamil Nadu

Experienced

EDUCATION

Present B. Tech: Computer Science with specialization in Cyber

Security

SRM Institute of Science & Technology - Chennai, Tamil Nadu

Mar. 2020 High School: PCM

Tagore Public School - Jaipur, Rajasthan

LANGUAGES

English Fluent Hindi Native Speaker

SKILLS

Bootstrap

HTML5 Adobe Illustrator Experienced Experienced CSS3 Adobe Photoshop Experienced Experienced **JavaScript FIGMA** Beginner Experienced React Experienced Adobe XD Experienced